https://www.snpinc.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyHome / Privacy PolicySynthetic & Natural Polymers understands that personal privacy is of utmost importance & all information you provide is confidential. We may collect your Internet Protocol (IP) Address to monitor the quality of website traffic. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. No personally identifiable information will be collected unless you specifically provide it to us, in which case we hold that information in strict confidence. The information collected will never be shared with any third party organizations unless ordered by a court of law.Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads by visiting your Google “Ads Settings”. We may use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online.Third party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website. We may use data from Google’s Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) to serve ads on sites across the internet. Third party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to serve ads on sites across the internet, based on your past visits to our website.We may use this anonymous information for remarketing, to display more relevant ads to you on other websites at a later time. You can opt out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the “Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Page“. Third parties such as Facebook may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from our website(s) and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads.Users can opt-out of the collection used for ad targeting. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information and partnered third party API’s for purposes of contacting you, sending you e-emails, or targeted ads based on your request for information. Contact Us Today »Contact Us Name*
Email*
Phone*
Product Category* Paper CoatingTextilesPrinting AdditivesBarrier CoatingsSpecialty ApplicationsOther
Product* Polyester Based EmulsionsSodium AlginateAqueous EmulsionsPolyvinyl AlcoholOther
Comments
This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply. Privacy Policy
